All-Japan Flying Circus
Fall Tournament
West Kyushu Qualifiers
It's time for the All-Japan
Flying Circus Fall Tournament!
We're at the West Kyushu qualifiers,
where Mashiro Udon's poster
girl, Arisaka Mashiro,
Arisaka Mashiro
Kunahama High 1st Year
Ichinose Rika
Takafuji Academy 1st Year
is currently facing Takafuji Academy's
hottest prospect, Ichinose Rika!
The two first-years, having
won their first-round matches,
are now facing off in an A Block
second-round matchup.
Which of these two will
progress to the third round?
See you later!
Point to Ichinose!
The first point is mine!
They're getting so excited
about a run-of-the-mill match.
On the other hand, our FC is sure
to elicit pin-drop silence.
If we win two tournaments in a row,
the FC community will be forced to admit...
That what we created is superior.
That our beautiful, perfect FC is superior.
Episode Eleven:
"I Refuse to Lose!"
In the A Block second-round
speeder-versus-speeder matchup,
Ichinose has drawn first blood!
She's going to pull away!
Remember, M-Mashiro-chan!
It's all about spirit!
Why are you so nervous?
Step on it, Mashiro!
And put your gameplan into motion!
Got it?
Y-Yeah!
Mashiro.
Let's both do our best in our match today.
Yeah! I'm coming for you
with everything I have!
Thank you, Rika.
It's all thanks to you that I managed
to find my own style of FC...
That I managed to get this far.
I didn't do anything.
You're the one who put in the
effort to make it this far.
Compared to how much effort you put
in, I've still got a ways to go.
But I refuse to lose!
I'll beat you this time for sure.
Good.
Bring it on.
Mashiro-chan's making her move.
Yeah.
Point to Ichinose! 0-2!
Ichinose now has a two-point lead!
Can Arisaka come back from this?
Where's Mashiro? I thought
she took a shortcut.
Above you!
Mashiro?!
I call this the Pickle Stone Tactic!
And I'm putting it in play!
"Pickle Stone"? Come on.
She'll put her opponent under pressure
by taking up position above her,
and then go for either her
back or the next buoy.
This is just like Inui-san's tactic!
Smart move, I must admit.
Goddammit! I wanted to face her!
Mind your language, young lady.
I-I'm sorry, milady!
She got a good read on Ichinose's
movements and got above her.
Here I come!
Got you!
Point to Arisaka! 1-2!
Point to Arisaka!
We're all tied up!
Arisaka scored two straight
points to level the score!
That's the way, Arisaka!
As a fellow speeder, I'll share
some of my spirit with you!
Only team members are allowed back here, Bro.
Take a shortcut to the fourth
line at once, Ichinose-san!
Okay!
I'm not letting you past!
You must stop her, no matter what.
Don't let her get away.
Got it!
A back punch?!
Nicely done.
Got your back!
Point to Ichinose! 2-3!
Ultimate Move: Mashiro Punch!
Point to Arisaka! 3-3!
Way to go, Mashiro!
This match is too close to call!
I haven't been taking on Misaki-senpai
or Asuka-senpai for show, you know.
I'll beat you this time for sure!
I want to win, too!
Ichinose-chan has gotten a lot
better at dogfighting since summer.
She must've practiced really
hard after losing to you.
They're both awesome!
Guess I should've learned more
lessons from my defeat, too.
Oh, come on, Bro.
We'll have to do our best
so they don't outshine us.
Yeah.
Time's running out!
Who will triumph in this one?
Takafuji's Ichinose, or Kunahama's Arisaka?
That match is still going?
Kunahama...
But I'm practicing really
hard right now so I can have
an exciting match with you next time.
So look forward to the fall tournament—
That's out of the question.
What's wrong, Saki?
Let's go.
Make a beeline for the first buoy, Mashiro!
Okay!
Oh, no, you don't!
Mashiro-cchi...
Point to Arisaka!
4-3!
This match is over! Arisaka wins!
Yay!
All right!
Atta girl, Mashiro!
Arisaka wins a hard-fought battle
to advance to the third round!
Arisaka Mashiro
Kunahama High 1st Year
Ichinose Rika
Takafuji Academy 1st Year
Arisaka Mashiro
Kunahama High 1st Year
You were great, Mashiro!
Rika...
I—
Congrats, Mashiro.
But I'll be the one to win next time.
That won't happen, Rika.
I'll have the last laugh next time, too.
Mashiro-chan played so well.
All right! Time to break a leg myself!
I'm gonna win, no matter what!
Right!
Mashiro Udon
Here's yer order!
It's hot. Be careful
not to burn yer tongue.
Let's eat!
So, how does that celebratory udon taste?
Delicious!
Aww, you bring a tear to my eye.
I wasn't talking to you, Mom.
Congrats, Mashiro.
I'll allow you to treat
me to udon to celebrate.
Stop that, Arika.
I'm sorry.
Fine by me!
Everyone who rooted for Mashiro
gets to eat on the house!
You're embarrassing me, Mom.
We've come to sample the offerings as well.
When I told them Mashiro Udon serves great
food, they wanted to try some.
Shindou-san!
I didn't know you were here to watch.
I am.
Partly to cheer my juniors on,
but also because I'm curious
about how Inui will play this time.
How are things, Hinata-kun?
I think we're as ready as we could be.
I'll be taking her on in the third round.
I shall eat some udon and make
sure I play with maximum spirit!
I'll have yer bowls ready right away.
A-Asuka-chan! You need to get
ready for the next match!
R-Right! I'd better hurry!
I'll eat some more and join you later.
They're such a lively bunch.
Stay on your toes, Aoi.
Where did that come from?
Kairyou Academy's Inui Saki and
her second, Irina Avalon...
Those two are no ordinary team.
Please.
We've known that since the summer tournament.
No, that's not all I'm talking about.
I bet they still have
something up their sleeves.
That Avalon brand bothers me.
Is this your instinct as an
experienced dealer talking?
There's something off about those Grav-Shoes.
I'll keep an eye out.
Kurashina wins!
Well played.
Thanks!
That flying fish-like barrel
roll was really pretty!
Where's Misaki-chan?
Over at B Block. Her next match begins soon.
She was having an udon-eating
contest until just now, though.
I hope she doesn't get an upset tummy.
But Shindou-san was something else.
I know, right?
He gobbled those noodles up like a Cobra.
This match is over!
Inui wins 8-0!
She's good! Way too good!
Inui once again used the Birdcage,
which dethroned Shindou,
to inflict a crushing defeat on Satouin!
That was perfect, Saki. Keep it up.
Okay.
The first day of the fall
tournament comes to close,
and all matches up to the third
round have been completed!
Shitou Suisan 2nd Year
Ganeko Mayu
In the A Block semifinals, Ganeko,
one of the favorites for the title,
Kunahama High 2nd Year
Kurashina Asuka
will face Kurashina, who pushed
Shindou all the way in summer!
Kairyou Academy 2nd Year
Inui Saki
And in the other semifinal in B Block, Inui,
after her overwhelming victory over Satouin,
Tobisawa Misaki
Kunahama High 2nd Year
takes on another rising star
from Kunahama, Tobisawa!
Sorry I was the only one
to lose in the third round.
Don't worry. You did great.
She's right, Mashiro-chan.
You put up a good fight against
Ganeko-san, who placed third in summer.
Misaki, you're going up
against Inui tomorrow.
I'm gonna show off the fruits of
all the training I've done and win!
And then, I'll play Asuka in the final.
Right!
I'll do my best, too!
Whoa!
They're leaving on that?
What's going on?
That's—
Oh, hello.
Inui-san!
Good work.
Saki hasn't had to work at all.
But I'm sure you're all exhausted,
so please do get some rest.
If not, Saki won't be able to
show the world a perfect victory.
You're assuming you're gonna win?!
Be seeing you, then.
Let us do our best tomorrow.
I <3 Misaki
Tobisawa Misaki for Life
Misaki Life
Okay!
I'm going to root for you with
all my heart, Misaki-senpai!
This isn't some idol concert, you know.
In Mashiro-chan's eyes,
this might just be a
Flying Misaki-senpai Show.
Allow me, Arisaka Mashiro, to
sing the official cheering song!
Fly across the starry sky
with your unrivaled wings.
Whoa, this is really firing me up!
I can't focus like this, so when you root
for me, do it where I won't see you.
Your answer is surely—
What? You meanie!
Don't you realize I'm doing
this out of love for you?!
Yeah, yeah.
You sure are full of energy
first thing in the morning.
Hello.
Inui-san!
Make as much noise as you want,
while you still can.
Because you will fall silent
once the match begins.
I wouldn't be so sure of that.
You never know how a match will go.
Well, I can't wait to find out.
See you.
Shitou Suisan 2nd Year
Ganeko Mayu
Kunahama High 2nd Year
Kurashina Asuka
This is the second day
of the fall tournament!
Kurashina is currently on top against Ganeko!
Milady!
Point to Kurashina! 2-5!
Go, Asuka-senpai!
You're too careless!
You seem full of spirit, Tobisawa-kun.
Shindou-san...
I look forward to great
things from your zipzapping.
Got it.
But really, I wanted to beat you
at that udon-eating contest.
I'll take you on anytime.
Then if I beat Inui-san,
I'll come for you next.
Point to Kurashina!
This match is over!
Kurashina wins!
In the A Block semifinal,
Kurashina eliminates Ganeko,
who placed third last time around,
Shitou Suisan 2nd Year
Ganeko Mayu
Kunahama High 2nd Year
Kurashina Asuka
to progress to her first-ever final!
Next up, we have the B Block semifinal!
Who will face Kurashina in the final?
Will be the Dominating Queen
of the Sky, Inui Saki,
or will it be the Wildcat
Fighter, Tobisawa Misaki?
Break a leg, Misaki-senpai!
If you win, we'll let you
have free udon for a year!
Settle down, Mashiro-cchi.
Hooray, hooray, Misaki-senpai!
Would you listen to me?
Misaki.
Scared?
I guess.
I mean, Inui-san destroyed Satouin-san.
And I could lose the same way.
I'll admit that I am pretty
scared of that prospect.
Misaki...
But it's because I lost that I could
take a long, hard look at myself.
And it's because I lost that
I could dedicate myself to FC.
Anyway, I'm gonna go on
the attack and stay there!
That is my brand of FC!
Yeah.
Inui-san...
I'm gonna break free of your Birdcage.
You'd best be prepared to zipzap.
On your marks...
Set!
Here we go!
Inui's heading for the buoy,
whereas Tobisawa immediately took a shortcut!
Point to Inui!
So it does come down to this after all.
Now, then.
What will you do, Tobisawa-kun?
Misaki.
Inui's looking to win all her matches
in this tournament with the Birdcage.
So...
you should be able to get
close to her from below.
Roger.
As always, I'm gonna look to get
down and dirty in a dogfight.
That's the way.
Once you get close, stick to her like glue
and break her down bit by bit!
The entire time?
This is gonna be a pain in the tail.
But quitting would be even worse!
Okay...
Here I go!
Whoa! Tobisawa with an insane burst of speed!
Come on, Inui-san. Let's zipzap.
Don't let her get away, Misaki!
I know!
Sonic Boost, eh?
She must've practiced a whole lot.
But...
No change in plans, Saki.
Push her down to the water.
Okay, Irina.
Inui suddenly stopped in her
tracks and blew Tobisawa back,
and now Tobisawa's falling!
I said, let's zip...
zap!
There's more!
Once more!
How's that? Did it fire you up some?
Saki...
Don't let her dictate the tempo.
I know.
This match is so like Misaki-senpai!
Yeah.
Oh, Tobisawa has been
forced down to the water!
She made it out of the water!
She isn't clear yet.
She hasn't broken free of the Birdcage yet.
Back and forth they go, trying to
secure an advantageous position above!
She's having trouble breaking free.
Not looking to get above me anymore?
H-Hey, you can't touch my back like this.
I see.
She's flying upside-down, huh?
Yeah, with her back facing away, she
won't be at a disadvantage in a dogfight.
Well, I certainly hadn't thought of that one.
But it should be difficult
to keep flying upside-down.
Yeah.
Which is why this could be the turning point.
Misaki-chan!
I'm not done yet!
Nice, Misaki!
Stay on the attack!
Easy for you to say!
Wow! Tobisawa is continuously attacking
Inui while flying upside-down!
I'm gonna go on the attack and stay there!
Saki?
That's...
Oh?
Point to Tobisawa! 1-1!
You're the best, Misaki-senpai!
She's evened the score!
That was the Cobra!
Tobisawa pulled off the Cobra from
an upside-down position to score!
Saki!
What do you think you're doing?
There's no place for such
unsightly play in our FC!
Yes, Irina.
I'm fighting with everything I've got!
What about you,
Inui-san?!
Everything...
What is this feeling?
She refuses to run and keeps coming at me.
My body's burning up.
I want to beat her.
I want to beat her in a dogfight.
Sorry, Irina.
Point to Inui!
She's good at dogfighting, too!
Ten seconds left!
This is scary,
but...
it's so much fun!
This match is over!
You're so cool, Misaki-chan!
I couldn't beat her.
Misaki...
I've never tasted such a
repulsive victory before.
Kunahama High 2nd Year
Kurashina Asuka
Kairyou Academy 2nd Year
Inui Saki
To Be Continued
Preview
Fly!
Just a bit more...
It is time for silence to descend upon us!
Let's keep flying together!
Episode Twelve:
"Let's... Keep Flying!!"